marocwebs.com 2015-03-21

# Hosting MarocWebs | Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy accredited to the hosting MarocWebs :

**In an effort to protect the privacy of data and the rights of our customers and visitors to the site, was created Privacy Policy and is explaining what information we collect when you do fill the registration form located in the hosting MarocWebs, and what do we do with this data and information, the hosting MarocWebs is committed to maintaining the privacy of data hosting clients and beneficiaries of its services, which aim to provide a safe and convenient for our customers to manage their websites comfortably and securely.**

Personal information :

**We in hosting MarocWebs collect information and data required and that is offered by the participants in our service and through the registration page in MarocWebs and we are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of the data and not to do with the participation of , sale or lease of such data with any other party , and as shown , data that we collect is limited to the name or title , email, country , and phone number , which is necessary to activate the service and communication with the subscriber.  
You can not share this data only with the relevant government agencies in the case of a binding court order , otherwise , all the data is kept in the strictest confidence .  
The hosting MarocWebs rely on e- mail address registered in the customer’s account as the identity of his background , in case of a request to change the account password, the client , this change is confirmed via e-mail for your account only .**

File reporting :

**With most sites we use this file reports and information which may contain IP address of your device, the type and version of your Internet browser, Internet Service Provider, the link through which you visit the site MarocWebs, the number of clicks and the names of the pages you’ve visited, all this is to analyze some of the information for the site and visitors, and this in order to learn hand and Visitors countries and their attitudes, including geographic and demographic system for visitors, with the knowledge of any of the information we collect does not contain any important information of your own .**

Cookies :

**Cookie is a very small part of the data that is stored in a visitor to connect to the client information to the server , we may use cookies temporary and persistent cookie , for cookie interim Once you close your browser or log out of your account we have , will be deleted cookies are full and final of the device, the persistent cookie is just a small text file stored on the hard drive of your computer for a period of time certain sets across our server , as there is some information in the help files for the browser you have to explain how the cookies and how to handle them and delete files permanent ones, because the hosting MarocWebs used some sessions cookies temporary reserves the way you liked the client that handles his personal account on the site MarocWebs , also helps us to reduce the download time of a server , giving you fast browsing the site , the persistent cookie is used to store some information , such as e-mail or your password , which is often used constantly when access to your accounts , and these files the customer can choose to either store or forget this data, knowing that the cookies be encrypted in a way do not indicate the personal owner at all.**

Advertisement :

**We use a company announcement as a third party to display ads, and when you visit our website, it is entitled to this company that uses information about your visits to this site (including your name, e-mail address or telephone number) in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you through a profile link DART (can prevent the use of the DART cookie via the browser), if you want to know the choices available to you to prevent the use of this information by this company and more information about our privacy policy for this site, please read this page carefully .**

**We hosting MarocWebs  [marocwebs.com](http://en.marocwebs.com/) We use Google AdSende, externally as a financial resource, so use Google Inc “[Cookies](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx)” To display ads on our site, and thus will be able to use Google’s cookie DART, from ads “by interests” users based on their visits to our sites, and of course to our visitors can disable the use of the DART cookie by visiting “[Privacy Policy Google ads and content network](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)” .**

**Add to this that some of the companies that advertise our partners may use cookies and web beacons , for example ( the company Google AdSense) , a company advertising the first in our site, of course, such companies which are declared and the third party in this privacy policy to inform such data and statistics via Internet protocols for the purpose of improving the quality of their ads and measure their effectiveness , as these companies and in accordance with agreements concluded with us are entitled to use other technologies (such as cookies, web beacons , and Beacons ” JavaScript ” ) for the same purposes mentioned above, which is in content development advertising for these companies , and measure the effectiveness of these ads , without any other goals may harm more or less users on the network .**

**It also you should check the privacy policy of the third party (the company declared “Google AdSense”) servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and their various activities,**  
**And to review the privacy policy of a company Google AdSense please “[Click here](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)” .**

**Note : The Google’s cookie store advertising in the user’s browser to understand the types of pages visited by the user,**  
**And this information is used to display ads based on interest categories that might bring users.**

**Finally, you can disable cookies through your individual browser options or when you log out of the site hosting .**  
**And if you need more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, you can get acquainted with them and by “[Clicking here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) ” .**
